topporn.com 2018-08-28

# Top Porn Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT CAREFULLY. BY YOUR USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE WITH THE POLICIES AND PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THE PRESENT PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS SITE.

The present Privacy Policy Statement details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information and/or data gathered regarding use of topporn.com. In addition, this Privacy Policy sets forth all relevant policies and practices for the sites.

## USE

This is an adult site that expressly and strictly limits its use to adults. This site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents on this site without exception. If you are under the age of 18 and/or under the age of majority in the jurisdiction you reside and from which you access the website, then your use will be terminated without notice or delay.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM USERS

Any customer that signs up as a member of the site will be required to provide personal information as well as demographic information which may include the name, e-mail address, username, and password. The site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database. In addition, other information such as IP address (es), referring website information, browser information, and other related data may be collected.

## DISCLAIMER

By the use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may use any personal information that has been provided by the user or that has been collected by the site about the user for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administrative, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading of personal data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the site or third parties authorized to use the information by the site.

By the use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

All personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the site. 

The site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. The site shall not be responsible for the privacy policy or the content of other such websites. This site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or privacy policies of any of those third-party websites.

Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the privacy policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the site.

All information collected may be shared when necessary to comply with applicable law and /or to cooperate with law enforcement agencies and the courts/tribunals.

A user's IP address may be used to diagnose problems with the server and all other technical issues and to administer the websites.

## SECURITY OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE

The site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the site.

While the website uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. All subscribers should consider any information provided to or collected by the site as non-confidential, and consequently the site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. The website uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information.

## "OPT-IN" & "OPT-OUT" PROVISIONS

"OPT-IN" -- Some offers may be presented to the subscriber with the option to express the subscriber�s preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes", the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information and data may be disclosed to third-parties.

"OPT-OUT" -- Other offers may be presented with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the offer) then the site may transfer the subscriber's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the offer. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the subscriber may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider.

## CHANGES/MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy may be changed, modified or edited at any time. It is the subscriber�s responsibility to verify the Privacy Policy intermittently to see if there has been any change. All changes to the privacy policy shall be in effect thirty days after it is posted, unless the terms of the privacy policy indicate otherwise.

## TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE

Each user should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of use for the site. By accepting membership to this site, you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this site to use information that it has gathered from user.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy statement please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
